Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to: Nellie and Theron, From: Harry and Zoe [Davis],July 6, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Marriage License (Gress and Hartring),June 30, 1904 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, Albion College Cadet Band,Spring 1921 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, Test,1922-1928 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, Finley Bank Book, Royal Bank of Canada, Aylesbury, Saskatchewan,undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, St. Patrick's Banquet, Morrice, Michigan,March 17, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous, Warranty Deed, Yellow Medicine, Minnesota,February 8, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, Report To Judge Russel,June 1, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, Jackson County School Letter,1917-1918 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to: NDF From: Universal Institute,June 24, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, Parma Township Ballot and Votes,1905 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, NDF, List of Christmas Presents,1898-1899 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis Recommendations,March 26, 1880 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous, Bale's Opera Rink, Lakeview, Playbill,March 27-28, 1891 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to: Grandma Finley From: Ruth,January 1954 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,December 10, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to: NDF From: Jerry and Theron Finley, Camp LeJunne, North Carolina,1949 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Classbook,undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Classbook,1886-1887 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, Auction Sale,April 10, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous, Auction Sale,November 7, [no year] (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, Wilson H. Davis, Notary Public,May 1, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, NDF, Cash Account,September 26, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous, Shakespeare Club,January 28, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis,September 20, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous, K.O.T.M. (Knights of the Maccabees) Banquet,June 27, 1891 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous, NDF, Physical Science Laboratory Notebook,1901 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous, Ford Motor Company, U.S. Map,undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,May-December 1923 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,December 1923-March 1924 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,March-May 1924 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,May-December 1924 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,December 1924-March 1925 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,March-May 1925 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin,December 1925-March 1926 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous, Geographic News Bulletin, Miscellaneous Photographs,undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Shopping Lists,May 3-September 14, 1892 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous, The Parma News,September 22, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous, Normal College News,April 9, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous, NDF, New Year's 1897 by Uncle and Auntie Herrick,January 1, 1897 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous, The Kalamazoo College Bulletin,1932 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous, Jackson County Official Fee Book,1900 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous, Probate Court Inventory of Personal Property,undated (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous, Buffalo Fertilizer Company Notepad,undated (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous, Notebook,undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - W.H. Davis, CLass Register,undated (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1888 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1889 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1890 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1889-1890 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1891 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Recitation Record,1890 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous, W. H. Davis, Class Register,undated (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous, Nellie M. Davis, Notepad,undated (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous, Nellie M. Davis, Students Notebook (volume 1 of 2),undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous, Nellie M. Davis, Students Notebook (volume 2 of 2),undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous, The Year 1888 Notebook,1888 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous, Autograph Book,undated (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous, Standard Miniature Notebook,undated (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous, Part of Place Booklet,undated (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous, ND, Oxford Notebook,undated (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous, Expense Account Record Book,undated (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Miscellaneous, Doll Scrapbook, Trade Cards,undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, Flower and Vase Scrapbook, Memorabilia (Bulletins and Newspaper Clippings, copies),undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Family Negatives, Correspondence to: Madame Queen From: Andy,undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings (Theme: War Through Women's Eyes),undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, Christoforo's Method for Mandolin (Music Instruction Book, copyright 1897, John Church Company),1897 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Teacher's Schedule Book,April 1900-June 1902 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, Justice of the Peace,undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, From Manager to Throne, by Rev. T. Delvitt Talmage,undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 77th Annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Instruction of the State of Michigan with Accompanying Documents for the Year 1913-1914, by Authority,1913-1914 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, Homestead on the Hillside, by Mary J. Holmes, copyright J. H. Sears and Company, Inc.,undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - ND, Age 12, Grammar Homework,1900 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ND, Report Cards,1895-1903 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NDF, Account Book,1916 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NDF, Composition Book,1916 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NDF, Examination Questions for 1920, Bulletin No. 3, State of Michigan, Department of Public Instruction,1920 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NDF, Marriage and Baby Announcement, and Hair, Invitation, and Newspaper Clippings,1912, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NDF, Receipts, 1917, 1945; Membership Cards, 1922,1945; Teaching Contract, Parma, 1931,1917, 1922, 1931, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NDF, Sketches,189u (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NDF, War Ration Book Four,[1940s] (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. W. H. Davis, 1901 From: Parma High School and 1908, 1924, 1927, includes Commencement Material from NDF,1901, 1908, 1924, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. Wilson H. Davis From: NDF,1912 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: friends and relatives, mostly while in Tuberculosis Hospital, Highland Park,1914-1915 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley Family From: Mr. and Mrs. H. E. Davis,1912-1925 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: ND From:, includes Name Plate,1898, 1911, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1916 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1918-1919 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1920 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1922 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1923 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1924-1925 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1926 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1925, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,1941-1945 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Many,undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Photograph Album, Devereaux School (Jackson County, Michigan),1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Photographs, Harry Finley, other children (8),1916, [1940s], undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Photographs, ND as a child (4),1895, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Photographs, ND, Parma High School Graduation (3),1904 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Photographs, NDF, Normal School at Ypsilanti (5),1908 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Photographs, NDF, as older lady, teacher, in California (10),1957, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Photographs, Parma Methodist Episcopal Church, interior,1904 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Postcards to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, 1928, 1935, and Invitation, 1900,1900, 1928, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Receipts of H. A. Duff, 1915-1916; Correspondence to Theron S. Finley re: Duff, 1912, 1916,1912, 1915-1917 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Souvenir Photographs to: Mrs. E. Davis,1907, to: Mr. Wilson L. Davis,1908 From: NDF,1907-1908 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Oversized folder 1, Certificates: ND and Theron S. Finley, Parma Marriage Certificate (printed form illustrated with colored flowers), July 3, 1912; ND Parma High School Diploma, printed and illustrated with handwriting, spotted, June 23, 1904; Gravure print? on board, spotted and battered, of Orlando de [H.] Moore, undated [post-Civil War],June 23, 1904; July 3, 1912, undated (Folder 1)